Finding Aid for University of Michigan Class Albums
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 1878 Class Album
  - Class
    - Norton, Albert James (Box 37)
      [3-9]
    - Owen, Charles Fernando (Box 37)
      [3-29]
    - Peck, Annie Smith (Box 36)
      [2-26]
    - Perrine, Charles Kendall (Box 36)
      [2-27]
    - Raymond, James Hervey (Box 36)
      [2-28]
    - Read, Jay Junius (Box 37)
      [3-14]
    - Reed, Louisa M. (Box 35)
      [1-23]
    - Ryan, Albert William (Box 36)
      [2-29]
    - Schurtz, Orr (Box 36)
      [2-30]
    - Shaw, James Truman (Box 36)
      [2-31]
    - Simonds, Ossian Cole (Box 37)
      [3-31]
    - Sizer, Frank Leonard (Box 37)
      [3-32]
    - Stringham, Douglass Houghton (Box 36)
      [2-32]
    - Swift, Sarah Elizabeth (Box 36)
      [2-33]
    - Terry, Hiram Everett (Box 37)
      [3-16]
    - Townsend, Cora Ilione (Box 36)
      [2-34]
    - Walling, Stuart Douglas (Box 36)
      [2-35]
    - Walmsley, Horace Bailey (Box 36)
      [2-36]
    - Whitehead, Andrew (Box 36)
      [2-37]
    - Wight, Sydney Buckminster (Box 37)
      [3-35]
    - Wilkins, Ross (Box 37)
      [3-10]
    - Willits, George Spencer (Box 36)
      [2-38]
    - Wrampelmeier, Theodore John (Box 36)
      [2-39]
    - Unidentified (Box 37)
      [3-3, 14, 17, 30, 33. 34]
  - Buildings
    - Univ. Hall, Mason Hall, South Wing, Rec./Lec. (Box 35)
      [1-26]
    - Haven and Mason Hall, Rec./LSG (Box 35)
    - University Hall, Rec./Lec. (Box 35)
      [1-27]
    - Haven Hall, Rec./Lec. (Box 35)
      [1-28]
    - Medical Building, Rec./Lec. (Box 35)
      [1-29]
    - Chemical Laboratory, Rec./Lec. (Box 35)
      [1-30]
    - University Hospital (Box 35)
      [1-31]
    - Observatory, U. of M. (Box 35)
      [1-33]
    - University Hall, Museums, Rec./Lec. (Box 35)
      [1-36]
    - University Hall, Class Room, Rec./Lec. (Box 35)
      [1-35]
  - Statues
    - Benjamin Franklin (Box 35)
      [1-34]
    - University Hall (?) (Box 35)
    - University Hall, Laoccon Group (Box 35)
      [1-40]
    - University Hall "Nydia" (Box 35)
      [1-37]
  - Ann Arbor views
    - Ann Arbor, General View (Box 35)
      [1-42]
    - Ann Arbor, State St., Meth. Ch. steeple (Box 35)
      [1-41]
    - Residence (Box 35)
      [1-43]
  - Group photos
    - Unidentified (Box 35)
      [1-25, 44, 45, 46]
- 1878 Class Album
  - Professors
    - Adams, C. K. (Box 38)
    - Angell, James B. (Box 38)
    - Campbell, J. V. (Box 38)
    - Cocker, B. F. (Box 38)
    - Cooley, T. M. (Box 38)
    - Denison, Charles S. (Box 38)
    - Frieze, Henry S. (Box 38)
    - Jones, C. N. (Box 38)
    - Langley, John W. (Box 38)
    - Morris, George S. (Box 38)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 38)
    - Steere, J. B. (Box 38)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [14, 17-18]
    - Walter, Edward L. (Box 38)
    - Williams, George P. (Box 38)
  - Students
    - Allen, M. B. (Box 38)
    - Angell, A. C. (Box 38)
    - Augur, W. W. (Box 38)
    - Barbour, F. A. (Box 38)
    - Bary, Minne (Box 38)
    - Benneson, Cora Agnes (Box 38)
    - Black, John H. (Box 38)
    - Butts, W. Henry (Box 38)
    - Byrd, Mary E. (Box 38)
    - Chandler, Eva (Box 38)
    - Colby, J. Rose (Box 38)
    - Cook, Webster (Box 38)
    - Danaher, Michael B. (Box 38)
    - Daugherty, C. M. (Box 38)
    - De Tar, Dave N. (Box 38)
    - Fleming, Randall Wade (Box 38)
    - Garrison, Frank (Box 38)
    - Gayley, Charles M. (Box 38)
    - Griggs, Clarence (Box 38)
    - Harrower, George H. (Box 38)
    - Horton, George (Box 38)
    - Hubbard, Edward H. (Box 38)
    - Jenks, Jerry W. (Box 38)
    - Jenks, W. L. (Box 38)
    - Knight, George W. (Box 38)
    - Moore, W. V. (Box 38)
    - Myrick, H. P. (Box 38)
    - Peck, Annie S. (Box 38)
    - Perrine, Charles K. (Box 38)
    - Ryan, Albert W. (Box 38)
    - Schurtz, Orr (Box 38)
    - Show, James T. (Box 38)
    - Stringham, Douglass H. (Box 38)
    - Swift, Sarah E. (Box 38)
    - Townsend, Cora Ilione (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [19-21]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [40-41]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [47-49]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [56-59]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [63-64]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [66-68]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [71-72]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [77-78]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [86-87]
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
    - Unidentified (Box 38)
      [93-94]
    - Walling, Stuart D. (Box 38)
    - Wamsley, Horace B. (Box 38)
    - Whitehead, A. (Box 38)
    - Willits, George S. (Box 38)
    - Wrampelmeier, T. J. (Box 38)
- 1882 Class Album
  - Faculty
    - Angell, J.B. (Box 39)
    - Cooley, Judge (Box 39)
    - Watson, James Craig (Box 39)
    - Frieze, Henry (Box 39)
    - Jones, Elisha (Box 39)
    - Cocker (Box 39)
    - Morris, George (Box 39)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 39)
    - Prescott, A.B. (Box 39)
    - Olney (Box 39)
    - Demmon, Isaac N. (Box 39)
    - Adams, C.K. (Box 39)
    - Walter, E.L. (Box 39)
    - Davis, R.C. (Box 39)
    - Stowell, Charles (Box 39)
- 1882 Class Album
  - Students
    (a number of photos are unidentified)
    - Campbell, Douglas H. (Box 39)
    - Hale, Al (Box 39)
    - Graham (Box 39)
    - Davenport, Frank (Box 39)
    - Robinson, Fred (Box 39)
    - Wilson, Harold (Box 39)
    - Coffin, Charles (Box 39)
    - Miller (Box 39)
    - Hyde, Lou (Box 39)
    - Gallaher, Jim (Box 39)
    - Baker, Frank (Box 39)
    - Shereer (?) (Box 39)
    - Oglesbee, Rollo (Box 39)
    - Betts, Fred (Box 39)
    - Tinsman, Homer (Box 39)
    - Unidentified (Box 39)
    - Shalding, H.E. (Box 39)
    - Herrick, James B. (Box 39)
    - Unidentified (Box 39)
    - Unidentified (Box 39)
    - Tyler (Box 39)
    - Tyler (Box 39)
    - Spencer (Box 39)
    - Shorer (?), Sam (Box 39)
    - Miller, Albert (Box 39)
- 1882 Class Album
  - Faculty and Students (Box 40)
- 1883 Class Album
  - Faculty
    (Photographs are not arranged in alphabetical order)
    - Adams, Charles Kendall (Box 41)
    - Adams, Henry Carter (Box 41)
    - Angell, James Burrill (Box 41)
    - Beman, Wooster Woodruff (Box 41)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre (Box 41)
    - Demmon, Isaac Newton (Box 41)
    - Denison, Charles Simeon (Box 41)
    - D'Ooge, Rev. Martin Luther (Box 41)
    - DePont, Paul Rousseau (Box 41)
    - Frieze, Henry Simmons (Box 41)
    - Harrington, Mark Walrod (Box 41)
    - Hennequin, Alfred (Box 41)
    - Hudson, Richard (Box 41)
    - Jones, Charles Nelson (Box 41)
    - Jones, Elisha (Box 41)
    - Langley, John Williams (Box 41)
    - Morris, George Sylvester (Box 41)
    - Olney, Edward (Box 41)
    - Payne, William Harold (Box 41)
    - Pettee, William Henry (Box 41)
    - Thomas, Calvin (Box 41)
    - Walter, Edward Lorraine (Box 41)
    - Wead, Charles Kasson (Box 41)
    - Winchell, Alexander (Box 41)
  - Students
    - Ames, Harry Stoddard (Box 41)
    - Ball Fanny Danforth (Box 41)
    - Banks, Archie Walter (Box 41)
    - Barnes, Edward Arthur (Box 41)
    - Bell, Julia Randolph (Box 41)
    - Benn, Emily Augusta (Box 41)
    - Berkey, Lillian Margaret (Box 41)
    - Berry, LaFayette Seavey (Box 41)
    - Black, Charles Hoge (Box 41)
    - Bliss, Walter Bond (Box 41)
    - Boyer, Arthur Albert (Box 41)
    - Brown Addison Makepeace (Box 41)
    - Brown: Edwin Newton (Box 41)
    - Burnett, Robert Newton (Box 41)
    - Chapin, Loomis Eaton (Box 41)
    - Clark, William George (Box 41)
    - Cole, Festus Clark (Box 41)
    - Comstock, John Josiah (Box 41)
    - Denny, Joseph Villers (Box 41)
    - Dott, Richard Millard (Box 41)
    - Duffield, Bethune (Box 41)
    - Dunlap, Frank Merrill (Box 41)
    - Edwards, William Milan (Box 41)
    - Eede, Edward West (Box 41)
    - Fall, Edmund Elwood (Box 41)
    - Fitzsimmons, Henry Allen (Box 41)
    - Garvin, Walter Brown (Box 41)
    - Gray, Ralph (Box 41)
    - Haff, Delbert James (Box 41)
    - Hall, George Chalmers (Box 41)
    - Hinsdale, Norman Dwight (Box 41)
    - Hodder, Frank Heywood (Box 41)
    - Hollingsworth, Emmet Louis (Box 41)
    - Hunt, Mary Elizabeth (Box 41)
    - Jennings, John Henry (Box 41)
    - Lee, George Waith (Box 41)
    - Leland, Frank Bruce (Box 41)
    - Lemon, Jeptha Elmer (Box 41)
    - Lightner, Clarence Ashley (Box 41)
    - Mace, William Harrison (Box 41)
    - Mack, Edwin Frederick (Box 41)
    - Mandell, Henry Addison (Box 41)
    - McDonald, Flora A. (Box 41)
    - Merrill, Leavitt King (Box 41)
    - Metcalf, Ralph C. (Box 41)
    - Miller, Albert Edward (Box 41)
    - Moore, Julian Coats (Box 41)
    - Morris, John J. (Box 41)
    - Morrow, Robert Groves (Box 41)
    - Moseley, Henry Elmer (Box 41)
    - Ohls, Henry Garnsey (Box 41)
    - Olcott, William James (Box 41)
    - Orcutt, Amy Alice (Box 41)
    - Payne, John William (Box 41)
    - Peers, Theodore Wing (Box 41)
    - Porter, Alice (Box 41)
    - Rhodes, Lewis Addison (Box 41)
    - Rohnert, Morse (Box 41)
    - Royer, Theodore Jr. (Box 41)
    - Smith, Carman Newcomb (Box 41)
    - Smith, Edwin Norton (Box 41)
    - Schoyer, Samuel Balkam (Box 41)
    - Stebbings, Walter Louis (Box 41)
    - Tuthill, Job (Box 41)
    - Tuthill, Samel Cooley (Box 41)
    - Twitchell, Ralph Waldo Emerson (Box 41)
    - Voight, Christine Louise (Box 41)
    - Walker, Fernando Arthur (Box 41)
    - Webster, Frank Lundy (Box 41)
    - Weir, Clara (Box 41)
    - Wilkins, Charles Trowbridge (Box 41)
    - Willard, Charles Dwight (Box 41)
    - Winship, John Thomas (Box 41)
    - Wright, Frederick Thompson (Box 41)
    - Class of 1883 (Box 41)
    - Class Reunion June 16, 1933 (Box 41)
- 1885 Class Album
  - 1885 Class Album (Box 42)
    (This album is in poor condition. The vast majority of photographs are unidentified on the pages, however, some May be identified on their backsides. Their removal from the pages of the album is often difficult.)
- 1887 Class Album
  - 1887 Class Album (Box 43)